
export const allQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following gases do not trap heat?",
    options: [
      "Carbon dioxide",
      " Nitrogen",
      " Water vapour",
      " Methane"
    ],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Earth has been cooler in the pre-industrial era than it is today?",
    options: [
      "a) True",
      "b) False"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "If you removed the atmosphere's natural greenhouse effect, and everything else stayed the same, Earth's temperature would be?",
    options: [
      " 28 to 33°C cooler",
      " 35 to 50°C cooler",
      " 10 to 15°C hotter",
      " None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "As per global climate targets, to what degree C should the temperature rise be limited to?",
    options: [
      " 3.5 degree C",
      " 1 degree C",
      " 1.5 degree C",
      " 3 degree C"
    ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following gases do not trap heat?",
    options: [
      " Carbon dioxide",
      " Nitrogen",
      " Water vapour",
      " Methane"
    ],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Earth has been cooler in the pre-industrial era than it is today?",
    options: [
      " True",
      " False"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "If you removed the atmosphere's natural greenhouse effect, and everything else stayed the same, Earth's temperature would be?",
    options: [
      " 28 to 33°C cooler",
      " 35 to 50 °C cooler",
      " 10 to 15 °C hotter",
      " None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "As per global climate targets, to what degree C should the temperature rise be limited to?",
    options: [
      " 3.5 degree C",
      " 1 degree C",
      " 1.5 degree C",
      " 3 degree C"
    ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who sets the Nationally Determined Contributions?",
    options: [
      " United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change",
      " Paris Agreement",
      " Each country",
      " None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Are NDCs legally binding?",
    options: [
      " Yes",
      " No",
      " Some elements are legally binding – ex. Prepare, communicate and maintain NDCs"
    ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How often are NDCs communicated and updated by countries?",
    options: [
      " 2 years",
      " 5 years",
      " 7 years",
      " 10 years"
    ],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What does India’s NDC focus on?",
    options: [
      " Reduction in emissions intensity of GDP",
      " Promote non-fossil fuel based energy sources",
      " Increase in forest and tree cover",
      " All of the above"
    ],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "By when does India aim to achieve net zero?",
    options: [
      " 2050",
      " 2070",
      " 2060",
      " 2040"
    ],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "How many Missions does the National Action Plan on Climate Change have?",
    options: [
      " 4",
      " 5",
      " 6",
      " 8"
    ],
    correct:3
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not the Mission of India’s National Action Plan on Climate Change?",
    options: [
      " National Mission for Sustainable Agriculture",
      " National Water Mission",
      " National Solar Mission",
      " National Electric Vehicle Mission"
    ],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How many states/ UTs have received funding under the National Green India Mission?",
    options: [
      " 15",
      " 20",
      " 10",
      " 8"
    ],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the Missions is Atal Mission on Rejuvenation and Urban Transformation a part of?",
    options: [
      " National Mission on Sustainable Habitat",
      " National Mission on Enhancing Energy Efficiency",
      " National Mission on Sustainable Himalayan Ecosystem",
      " None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "How many climate change cells have been set up as a part of the National Mission on Strategic Knowledge for Climate Change?",
    options: [
      " 20",
      " 12",
      " 13",
      " 25"
    ],
    correct: 2
  }
  ];